name: 'singular and plural, a/an, the'
questions:
  -
    question: 'It’s $ pen.'
    answers:
      - a
      - the
      - an
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'They’re $ photos.'
    answers:
      - a
      - an
      - –
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'It’s $ umbrella.'
    answers:
      - a
      - an
      - –
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'Open $ door!'
    answers:
      - a
      - an
      - the
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'They’re $ chairs.'
    answers:
      - –
      - a
      - an
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'It’s $ email.'
    answers:
      - an
      - a
      - –
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'They’re $ laptops.'
    answers:
      - a
      - –
      - an
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They’re $ .'
    answers:
      - dictionarys
      - dictionaris
      - dictionaries
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'It’s $ ID.'
    answers:
      - a
      - an
      - –
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'It’s $ watch.'
    answers:
      - a
      - an
      - –
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'They’re $ .'
    answers:
      - watch
      - watchs
      - watches
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'What are they? $ books.'
    answers:
      - 'They is'
      - They’re
      - It’s
    correct: 2
